{"QandAs":[
 {"id":"1",
 "question":"How many answers are there in page 27 Exercise 1.2.2?",
 "answer":"9"},
 {"id":"2",
 "question":"What is the tips number in page 78?",
 "answer":"6"},
 {"id":"3",
 "question":"What is the first underlined Uva question on page 25?",
 "answer":"00403"},
 {"id":"4",
 "question":"How many questions/Exercises in page 47 has a '*'?",
 "answer":"8"},
 {"id":"5",
 "question":"How many points of 'Tips 6 Optimizing your coding' are there in page 78 and page 79?",
 "answer":"12"},
 {"id":"6",
 "question":"What is the first Uva question number mentioned in page 86?",
 "answer":"11935"},
 {"id":"7",
 "question":"In page 126,what is the content in the bracket() next to the title '4.2.5 Topological Sort'?",
 "answer":"Direct Acyclic Graph"},
 {"id":"8",
 "question":"What is the content of the largest title on page 133?",
 "answer":"4.2.9 Finding Strongly Connected Component (Directed Graph)"},
 {"id":"9",
 "question":"what is the algorithm discussed on page 155?",
 "answer":"Floyd Warshall's Algorithm"},
 {"id":"10",
 "question":"How many questions on page 197 without a '*' and underlines?",
 "answer":"24"},
 {"id":"11",
 "question":"On page 216, there are 2 largest titles, what is the content of the second one?",
 "answer":"5.5.8 Modulo Arithmetic"},
 {"id":"12",
 "question":"On page 248 there are 2 algorithm inventors, what is the number of citations of paper written by the second inventor in 1990?",
 "answer":"24000"},
 {"id":"13",
 "question":"How many triangles are there in page 279?",
 "answer":"4"},
 {"id":"14",
 "question":"How many circles are there from page 277 to 280?",
 "answer":"7"},
 {"id":"15",
 "question":"How many digrams are there on page 291?",
 "answer":"6"},
 {"id":"16",
 "question":"When was the photo on page 298 taken?",
 "answer":"2007"},
 {"id":"17",
 "question":"What is the total number of Exercises on page 311?",
 "answer":"21"},
 {"id":"18",
 "question":"What is the figure number on page 315? e.g X.Y",
 "answer":"8.11"},
 {"id":"19",
 "question":"Is there a figure on page 322? Yes/No",
 "answer":"No"},
 {"id":"20",
 "question":"What is the word on the deep color ballon held by Steven at page 334?",
 "answer":"IBM"},
 {"id":"21",
 "question":"What is the Chinese Proverb on page 335?",
 "answer":"Learning is a treasure that will follow its owner everywhere."},
 {"id":"22",
 "question":"How many vertices are there in the graph on page 350?",
 "answer":"8"},
 {"id":"23",
 "question":"What is the content of the biggest title on page 366?",
 "answer":"DP Speed-up with Matrix Power"},
 {"id":"24",
 "question":"What is the figure number on page 388? e.g X.Y",
 "answer":"9.13"},
 {"id":"25",
 "question":"What is the sum of 3 numbers in the table on page 392?",
 "answer":"153"},
 {"id":"26",
 "question":"How many terms are there in the Bibliography on page 398-401?",
 "answer":"71"},
 {"id":"27",
 "question":"What is the largest page number of this book?",
 "answer":"423"},
 {"id":"28",
 "question":"What is the largest Uva number on page 421?",
 "answer":"11984"},
 {"id":"29",
 "question":"How many pages are there in the Content part of this book?",
 "answer":"5"},
 {"id":"30",
 "question":"How many distinct First Letters (e.g ABC, A is the first letter) are there in the Abbreviation of this book?",
 "answer":"17"},]}